NOR FARAHANA BT KAMIS



CONTACT

- +6013 2309992
- farahannakamis@gmail.com
- 90C, Jln Hijrah 6, Kampung Melayu, Sungai Sering Bukit Antarabangsa 68000 Ampang

SKILLS

- · Inventory Management
- Supply Chain Management
- Supplier Relationship Management
- Contract Negotiation
- Strategic Sourcing
- Financial Acumen
- Time Management
- Proficient in MS Office i.e Excel, Word,
 PP, Buku & Autocount Software
- Bilingual i.e Malay and English

EDUCATION

Bsc PROPERTY MANAGEMENT (With Distinction)

Universiti Teknologi Malaysia

2018 - 2022 (Part-time)

DIPLOMA IN PROPERTY MANAGEMENT

Unifield International College, Universiti Teknologi Malaysia

2013 - 2016

REFERENCE

MOHD KASTURI

Senior Finance Manager +6017 3185651

PROFILE

30 year old motivated, versatile and proactive professional with over 7 years of experience and a track record of proven results and success in sourcing, purchasing, vendor relations, and contract negotiations. Seeking a position in which I can utilise my skills, abilities and experience to contribute to the company's success. Acknowledged for taking initiative, for working well under pressure and for being a team player.

EXPERIENCE

EXECUTIVE & COORDINATOR (PATI)

Profound Radiance Sdn Bhd, Malaysia

2017 - 2018

- Led impactful awareness campaigns for the Program Pendatang Asing Tanpa Izin, driving a notable increase in voluntary surrender and repatriation rates among undocumented immigrants.
- Collaborated with government agencies, NGOs to ensure program success and compliance with legal standards.
- Orchestrated travel arrangements and paperworks for the participants.
- Evaluated program efficacy, leading to

EXECUTIVE & COORDINATOR (PLATE NUMBER)

Crystal Site Sdn Bhd, Malaysia

2018 - 2020

- Managed vehicle plate numbers and organised a comprehensive database of registered vehicles.
- Responsible for managing the sale of vehicle registration plate numbers including facilitating transactions between buyers and sellers of personalised or specialised license plate numbers.
- Delivered exceptional customer service, detailed reports and financial statements.

EXECUTIVE & COORDINATOR (SUPPLY CHAIN)

International Sports Nutri-one (ISN-One)

2021 - 2024

- Managed end-to-end logistics operations, ensuring timely and cost effective solutions.
- Identified and onboarded reputable suppliers, enhancing procurement processes.
- Worked on forecasting demand, managing inventory, and coordinating logistics to ensure timely and cost-effective delivery of goods.
- Maintained accurate documentations for shipments and tenders, ensuring compliance.